This series is crafted for the purpose of entertainment.
All characters, behaviors, settings, and events depicted in this drama are entirely fictitious.
They are not designed to allude to any particular entity, occupation, or group of people.
Viewer discretion is advised.
[North Star Entertainment]
[7HD Channel]
[iQIYI]
[Present]
♫Where’s that love people are saying?♫
♫To always be by each other’s sides♫
♫The love that’s willing to sacrifice everything♫
♫Everything even my own life♫
♫Do they really exist? I’d rather not believe it♫
♫I don’t think I’ll ever fall for anyone♫
♫Love? I don’t find it interesting♫
♫Sorry about that♫
♫But then who are you?♫
♫To make my heart keep fluttering♫
♫Please tell me♫
♫What’s happening with my heart?♫
♫It can’t be, why am I feeling this?♫
♫Oh, my heart is pounding so fast♫
♫Time freezes whenever I see you♫
♫I wonder why every time you smile♫
♫Something in your eyes make me go weak♫
♫Oh no, this is real–it’s not a dream♫
♫Or is the love that people are saying...♫
♫Is it you?♫
[Flaming Chains of Love]
[Previously]
Are you and Fai seeing each other?
- No!
- No, Boss Rose!
There’s no way I’d be interested in this girl.
What you said was nothing but rude.
I’m sorry I said those things to you.
It’s okay. I’m used to it.
I’m really sorry.
Isn’t she pretty, Fai?
She’s just okay.
Men will be lining up to talk to her.
Are you Kaphrao?
Nod!
Phrao!
You two seem really close.
We played together, ate together, and even slept on the same bed.
Let’s go talk in your room after this.
You can just stay over in my room.
I plan to build an accommodation there. I want you and Kaphrao to take a look at it.
That’s all right.
I go there quite often.
I already have an idea what needs to be done.
I want to go there.
Wow!
We’re almost there.
-  Where is it?
- Over there.
- Off you go.
- Careful there.
Dad, let’s go. Hurry up.
Yeah, yeah, I’m coming.
Careful, Dad.
You come up too.
- Yeah.
- Come, let me help.
- Let’s go.
- Let’s go, Dad.
Hurry up, Dad. Be careful too.
Oh, hi, Aunt Ju!
Aren’t you a sight for sore eyes?
Aw, I’m flattered.
Mum!
- Bua!
- Mum!
Mum!
- What brings you all here?
- Miss you!
- Miss you too.
- Mummy…
Aw, sweetie.
Hello, Aunt Phaka.
Hello.
So, has this brat caused the Master any trouble, Young Master?
Not at all. She’s been a great help.
Told you, Mum.
How are you doing, Aunt Phaka?
I’m good, thank you. Oh, who’s this pretty lady here?
Is she your guest, Young Master?
This is Kaphrao. My dad has sent her here to help with work.
I see.
Mum, she’s the girl I told you about–my roommate.
- Oh, the one you said she’s very pretty in person?
- Yes!
- That’s her?
Really pretty indeed.
I’m Phaka, Bua’s mother.
Hello.
Since you’re already here, come and help me in the kitchen.
I’ll prepare something for Young Master.
Geez, Mum.
Stop whining.
I’ve just arrived here!
Good luck, girl.
Are you going to stay over here tonight? I’ll tell Phaka to prepare the cabin for you.
I don’t think so. I’ll just show her around and then we’ll go back.
I see.
Then, please come eat with us before you leave, okay?
Of course, thank you for inviting us.
Oh, it’s a pleasure.
Enjoy your day then.
Follow me.
How’s it? Got a lot there?
Wow!
Still loves to poke around like when she was seven.
Did you say something?
Nothing.
This is my family’s private island.
Dad lets the villagers live here for free.
But in return, they must look after the island for us.
It’s so beautiful–so natural.
Be careful, you might get cut. The shells are quite sharp.
Do you think I’m a kid or what?
Oh, right! I totally forgot you’re an expert sent by my dad.
Of course, I’m here to work not to pick a fight like someone around here.
Anyway, is the princess’s cabin far?
Wanna go back?
I was just asking.
Hey, what did you do? I saw that.
Are we there yet?
Stop whining or just go back.
We’re here.
Wow!
This is Lom and Miss Blew’s cabin.
It holds a lot of their memories.
So cute!
That time when the traitors were after Miss Blew, Lom as her bodyguard brought her to hide here.
Wow, that was quite far away.
But those thugs still found out and came after them.
Bullets were flying everywhere. They could barely escape just like a scene in an action movie.
Lom even got shot and fell into the sea. Fortunately, Miss Blew jumped off the boat to save her.
Otherwise, my sister would’ve turned into a sea ghost.
Awesome! You sure know a lot about it.
Because I was there too.
Don’t lie.
I’m serious. Why would I lie?
Hey, can I go up and have a look around?
Sure, go ahead.
Wow, so pretty.
There’s a bed too?
And clothes. Does that mean someone lives here?
They’re Lom and Miss Blew’s.
They often come here when they have free time. That’s why they’re quite close to the villagers here.
Wow, it’s wonderful.
Look, why don’t we build more cabins like this one?
And use the Princess of Madelin’s story as a selling point.
So that visitors who come to stay here would have a similar experience.
I’m sure the newly built cabin would look even more amazing.
But…
But what?
If we turn this island into a tourist attraction, I’m afraid it might affect the villagers’ way of living.
More visitors means this place will become less peaceful.
I’m surprised you care about other people too.
What? Didn’t you say this island is yours?
I’m afraid you’d just do anything as you please.
It’s true that I own this island, but I’m not a selfish person.
Unlike someone who only believes that the owner is nothing but a crook.
What else do you think we can use as a selling point?
We have pink seashells here.
Wanna see it?
This beach is special. If you find a pink seashell, you’re allowed to make one wish.
Really?
Yeah, why don’t you try to find one?
So silly.
What did you just say?
Look, so many seashells here!
Are you sure there’s one? I only see white or cream shells.
Oh!
What colour is it?
Are you colour blind? It’s brown!
Hey, look! I found it!
How’s that possible?
What?
I mean, I didn’t expect you’d find it.
Can I make a wish now?
Yeah, go on.
May the project we’re about to do here become successful.
And may everyone be happy.
What the hell did you wish for? Look what happens!
I…
What the…?
There’s a cave over there! Let’s go!
Geez! Suddenly pouring down like that?
It’s during the monsoon season. We get more rainy days than sunny ones.
But it’s quick to pass by.
But it’s still pouring buckets. How are we gonna go home then?
We have to wait until it stops, obviously–you nitwit.
Hey, I asked you nicely.
And I answered you nicely too.
But you just called me nitwit–I don’t like it!
You nitwit.
Buffalo Fai!
Wait, whose is this?
When I want some alone time on the island, I’ll either set up a tent outside or sleep in this cave.
Do you think you’re a hermit or what?
It’s called being indie!
Hello?
Hello, Young Master. Where are you right now?
In the cave around the back of an island.
The storm just hit and it’s raining so heavily. I’ll go get you there.
No need. It’s too dangerous if you come out now. I’ll go back once the rain lets up.
Okay then. But if there’s anything unusual, please call me right away, Young Master.
Yes, please don’t worry.
Yes, Young Master.
So, when will the rain stop?
If it keeps raining, we might have to sleep here.
What? Here?
I’m not a hermit like you.
You’re the one who wants to come here in the first place.
Hey.
Get changed or you might catch a cold.
Into this cave-rotten shirt?
Then go ahead and let yourself freeze to death.
Hey! What are you doing?
Changing, obviously.
Do it somewhere else then!
Look around, where else can I do it? In the middle of the rain?
Geez!
What have I done to get this karma?
Hey.
What? Are you shy?
What? No.
But you’re blushing.
We ran a long way from there.
Fine, change into this then.
But if you’re shy, just do it behind that rock.
Are you done?
Shut up.
You’ll get to sleep in a tent for sure.
Go away.
Sitting there alone, you might get spooked.
So? I’ll knock its teeth out!
Young Master!
Bua!
I’m here!
The rain has let up so Dad told me to come and get you.
Here, take it.
You too.
Let’s go then.
So, it stopped raining just like that? Unbelievable.
The sea in the south is always like that.
The storm is pretty bad today. The waves are probably too strong to go offshore.
You’d better stay here tonight, Young Master.
What? Does that mean we won’t be able to go back until tomorrow, Bua?
I’m not sure either. Sometimes, the storm lasts for days.
Or even three to four days. The worst case I’ve experienced was a week.
Damn it.
Please make yourself comfortable then. I’ll go get dinner ready.
Don’t you dare make that face, you silly Gremlin.
We’re stuck here all because you were being stubborn.
Let’s see if Lom has left any clothes here.
Here, change into this.
I’m not using someone else’s belongings without their permission.
If you’re so puffed up with your pride, then just stay rotten in that outfit.
I’m going to shower and get changed. We’re stinking like a walking dustbin.
Your face also stinks!
If you change your mind, just follow me.
Just make it quick, I don’t like to wait. And don’t forget to wash your hair–it got wet from the rain.
You hardly have anything to protect your brain.
Then, go shower first so that you won’t keep rushing me.
I’ll wait here. Be quick.
You also know how to be nice, huh?
Don’t you have anywhere else to stay?
Stop being so fussy, silly Gremlin.
Or do you want to go sleep in the cave? Go on then.
I just don’t want to sleep here with you!
As if you’ve never done it before.
Back then, I had to throw you out of my room almost every day.
I’m going to sleep.
If you’re going to stay there, just be a guard dog all night.
Is she already asleep?
Damn you! Hogging it all to yourself.
Fai and Kaphrao went to the island?
Yes. Uncle Boonsong just sent word that Miss Kaphrao wanted to take a look around the island.
But the storm suddenly hit, so both of them have to stay over on the island tonight.
Has anyone told Panee about this?
- She should know it by now.
- Ak!
Why did you leave my niece with that girl again?
Just you wait. If my niece’s got even a tiny scratch on her, that Athittaya girl must be responsible for it!
Calm down, Panee.
Your niece is my daughter too. I’m also worried about her.
You’re always taking that girl’s side. You love her more than your own child.
It’s because you’re like this, that’s why Fai always gets me wrong!
That girl keeps bringing Fai troubles.
That’s why I want Fai to stay away from her.
Have you ever asked her if that’s what she wants?
I’ve always chosen the best for her–because I love her the most!
Go talk downstairs.
We can go on land today?
Yes, Dad told me to let you know that he’ll leave here before noon to take you and Miss Phrao home.
There isn’t any storm coming today, right?
That’s right.
Then, please go tell Uncle Boonsong this–
Or would you rather leave right now, Young Master?
Nope.
Okay.
Having a good time?
I thought you’d wake up tomorrow morning.
Get up then.
Stop dawdling and go shower so we can have breakfast.
The sky is so bright.
That means we can go back today, right?
Not yet.
Why? The sky is looking so bright today.
No idea. Go ask Uncle Boonsong if you want to know.
But I don’t want to get stuck here anymore. Just one day is more than enough.
So? But you have to stay anyway.
Just blame it on yourself because you didn’t heed my advice.
Oh! But if you’re dying to leave here, you can try swimming to shore instead.
If I could, I would’ve done it since yesterday.
Blah, blah, blah!
What a jerk!
[Bua]: Want some crab?
[Boongsong]: Eat all you like.
[Phaka]: Go on, dear. I made them especially for you.
[Boonsong]: This is good.
[Bua]: Mum’s cooking is the best.
Can’t we go back today?
Sure, you can.
[Bua and Boonsong]: NO!
We can’t do that. We can’t go offshore today. The storm is hitting pretty hard.
But the sky looks so bright to me though.
- Yeah.
- Well,
D…Don’t let the sky fool you. Trust me, the storm is now forming right in the middle of the sea.
Yeah.
Yeah, that’s right.
Look there. It’s so windy, isn’t it?
The wind is so strong even a crab gets blown off the rock.
The crab was so shocked. I saw it with my own eyes, Dad.
- Really?
- Really, Mum.
The crab was shocked?
Yes! You can literally see its eyes wide open.
It was holding on to the rock for life, fighting the strong wind all night long. That’s why.
That’s right. If we leave right now, we might get blown off course and go all the way to Malaysia.
We can’t risk it.
Yeah, we’ll get blown away for sure. Can’t risk it.
Once the storm has passed, we’ll be able to leave.
That’s right.
Let’s eat.
- Eat all you like, Miss.
- Yeah.
Actually, it’s quite nice being stuck here on the island. It’s giving off such a romantic vibe.
Don’t you think so, Young Master?
Let’s eat.
- Yeah, let’s eat.
- Go on.
[Bua]: Nothing, Mum. Let me get this for you. There.
[Bua]: Here you go.
[Bua]: Dad, what do you want?
[Boonsong]: Kaeng Som*. (*Sour and Spicy Curry)
[Fai miming]: Eat!
[Boonsong]: Thanks.
Quit making a long face.
People here might think I’m not treating you well.
But I want to go home.
Tomorrow morning, Uncle Boonsong will take us home.
Really?
Why would I lie?
Finally, I’m going home!
Tell me honestly, do you really hate being stuck here with me that much?
Yes, you also feel the same, don’t you?
Of course!
It’s been over 24 hours. I can’t wait to get you out of my face!
So annoying!
Hurry up! Don’t you know it’s rude to keep the older ones waiting?
Get up!
What the hell is wrong with her?
Guys, here comes the squid!
- Squid?
- Here you go.
Yes, go ahead and dig in.
Wow, looks yummy.
My throat is burning already.
- Easy there.
- It’s burning.
I’m stuck here on this island because of you.
It’s all your fault!
Stop saying the same thing over and over again–it’s so annoying!
Because you’re stubborn and never listen to a damn thing I say.
Say it to yourself first.
You’re getting so wasted you might drown in your own puke.
Drown in my own puke?
You really don’t know me, huh?
What a smart mouth. Wanna try it?
Go away. You reek of alcohol!
Come on, don’t play innocent.
No! Go away!
There she goes!
Here, Young Master. One more.
Want some more, babe?
No!
What? Chicken out, huh? Does that mean you’re a wimp?
Give it here!
Oh, she’s up for it now.
She’s not a wimp, guys!
Here, Young Master. I’ll top it off for you.
Come on, let’s do a round, guys!
Just half a glass for you, Mum.
Cheers!
Down it!
Loser!
Ha! We’ve just started, babe.
- Bring it on!
- Cheers!
Come then.
Do you dare?
Bring it on.
- Dad and Mum, you do it too.
- Look!
Mine is empty too!
[Kaphrao]: Can you do it?
Watch me!
Come on!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Ten!
We already count to ten. You lose!
What kind of bar was that? Stop talking nonsense.
It’s you who should stop talking nonsense.
Can’t you just walk properly?
I am…
walking so straight.
You’re just all talk.
I’m the best in the world.
Can you please walk properly?
I’m doing it.
Geez, try to be more helpful, will you?
[Young Kaphrao]: Please let me sleep in your room.
Go away!
Please let me sleep in your room, Fai!
But I don’t want to!
But I’ve never slept alone. I’m scared!
Fai, please open the door!
Fai!
Please open the door!
I’ve never slept alone. I’m scared!
Fai, I’m scared!
Fai, please open the door! I’m scared!
Fai! I’m scared, Fai!
I’ve never slept alone!
You nitwit! Are you going to stand here and cry all night?
If you don’t stop crying, I will not let you in.
Go sleep over there. If you touch me, I’ll throw you out of here.
Got it?
Yes.
Do you hate me that much?
I'm sorry.
What the heck? What did you do?
What? I didn’t do anything!
You were so drunk last night.
So what? Did we sleep together?
Are you nuts? How could you say something like that?
That hurts!
You’re hurting me, Gremlin!
It hurts! Stop!
That’s because you said something disgusting! Gross!
Look who’s talking.
I know you tried to take advantage of me last night, didn’t you?
I didn’t do it!
Are you sure? I woke up and your arm was wrapping around me.
It was you who got drunk and tried to molest me last night.
Don’t be ridiculous. Do you have proof?
I do though–with my own eyes.
I don’t fancy you for even one bit!
Ha! As if I were too!
Fine! Whatever!
Go then! What are you waiting for?
[Hold On Together Shop]
Oh, you’re here? How are you feeling, Young Master?
Have you sobered up now?
Yes, much better.
Young Master! Young Master!
Wait for me too.
I thought you wouldn’t go back with us this time.
I wouldn’t miss it.
- Dad, Mum…
- What now?
I’m leaving.
- Look at her.
- Aren’t you staying?
Stop complaining. Give me a hug!
Love you, Dad!
- You too, Mum.
- Come, dear.
I wonder who she’s taking after.
Her mother, of course.
I promise that next time when I come back, I’ll bring you sons-in-law–how about ten of them?
- Whoa!
- As you wish!
Hey, don’t encourage her!
Who cares? If she wants to, just let her be.
But make sure you do your work for Young Master too. Don’t just go flirting around and cause her trouble.
I know, Mum.
Bring me three or four, maybe.
You got it.
Bring one for me too.
Don’t even think about it.
Geez, I was just kidding.
Miss Kaphrao, please come visit us again.
Of course. If I have a chance, I’ll definitely drop by.
This place is really nice and so beautiful.
Don’t worry, you’ll get to come here again for sure.
Dad wants you to help me with this project, you’ll get to come here until you’re sick of it.
If it’s about work, I’ll never back down.
Good!
Let’s go then. The sun is getting stronger.
Hey, not so fast!
- Don’t run, dear. You might trip over.
- Silly girl.
Exactly like her mother.
Stop talking nonsense!
Be careful!
Don’t worry, Dad! This is nothing.
That’s all right. I can manage.
Come on. I don’t want you to have an excuse to complain to my dad if you fall off the boat.
Hurry up.
♫I could never forget those eyes of yours♫
♫The warmth you used to give me, I still remember it vividly♫
♫No matter for how long, you’ll always remain in my heart♫
♫All those years I’ve been waiting, for us to finally be together again♫
Good luck!
- Bye Bye!
- Have a safe trip.
Please take care of yourself!
Okay.
I’ll bring you a son-in-law next time!
Good luck, dear.
They’re gone.
Our rascal Bua.
Bye, dear! Good luck!
Fai is back?
Yes. But right now, she’s discussing work with the Master and Miss Kaphrao.
My niece has just got back from a long trip, what’s there to talk about?
No idea too. But it probably won’t take long. She’ll be home soon.
What should we have for dinner, Miss Phrao?
I’ll let you choose today.
Sure.
Athittaya.
Haven’t I warned you not to cause Fai any trouble?
If it’s about getting stuck on the island, I can explain.
Don’t talk back to me! You’re as rude as ever.
Miss Panee, the storm was terrible indeed.
We couldn’t leave the island–as if the sky were tumbling–
Who asked you? Don’t butt in. Just get lost.
Yes, Miss.
You put my niece in trouble and also in danger.
I’m sorry.
Sorry again?
I’m sick of hearing this word from you.
Then, what do you want me to do?
You ask for it yourself.
Young Master, please stop!
Please stop!
What is it, Bua?
Young Master, you…
you need to help Miss Phrao.
Miss Panee is so mad at Miss Phrao for taking you away from her for many days.
So, she punishes her.
Is it that bad?
Yes, you need to go talk to Miss Panee and help Miss Phrao.
I feel bad for her.
I don’t think she’d listen to me.
Young Master!
But don’t worry. I’ll find a way to help her.
Panee punishes my Little One?
Yes, she’s in the garden right now.
At this rate, you’ll probably finish it next year.
What are you doing?
Cooking, maybe? Wanna eat it?
If Miss Panee sees us together, she’ll be more furious.
I already have a lot on my shoulders.
Please don’t make it worse for me.
It’s also my fault that you got punished.
So, I’ll take half of the punishment too.
What are you looking at? Go scoop up the grass!
Back then, it was you, wasn’t it?
Pluck out all the weeds. Don’t go home if you can’t finish it.
Phrao. It’s lunchtime. Let’s eat, dear.
Are you tired?
How is this possible?
Back then when I got punished, you were the one who helped me, weren’t you?
I didn’t do anything wrong back then. Why would I help you?
Then, if you know that person who used to help me, can you please say ‘thank you’ to her for me?
Can’t do that.
Thank you.
I said I can’t do that.
That was for you.
♫But then who are you?♫
♫To make my heart keep fluttering♫
♫Please tell me♫
♫What’s happening with my heart?♫
♫It can’t be, why am I feeling this?♫
♫Oh, my heart is pounding so fast♫
♫Time freezes whenever I see you♫
♫I wonder why every time you smile♫
Something in your eyes make me go weak♫
♫Oh no, this is real–it’s not a dream♫
♫Or is the love that people are saying...♫
♫Is it you?♫
Stop, stop.
Go that way! There’re still lots of weeds there.
Fai is here to help my Little One. There’s nothing to worry about now.
It’s a good sign, isn’t it?
I hope things will get even better in the future–as it should’ve been a long time ago.
Let's go.
Fai.
The ground is dirty, don’t just lie down like that? Get up.
I’m totally beat. Let me stay like this for a while.
I did most of the work there.
So? I didn’t ask for your help.
You were so slow. If you’d done it alone, it would’ve taken years to finish it.
Fine, go on and stay like that. I’m leaving.
Hey, are you really going to leave me here? I came to help you.
Then, get up. Get up!
♫Those times we used to be happy together♫
♫I still cherish every minute of them♫
♫But I don't know if you also feel the same♫
♫Those things in the past, I still can’t forget them♫
♫I want to know if you’re like that too–do you also feel the same?♫
♫I could never forget those eyes of yours♫
♫The warmth you used to give me, I still remember it vividly♫
♫No matter for how long…♫
[Next Episode]
I also ordered Nambang chicken for you.
Aunt Panee made me go on a blind date this morning.
How was it?
Don’t you feel anything at all that I went out with someone else?
I was going to give you some advice on how to pursue a girl.
So, what should I do?
Do you want to go to the dam with me?
The dam?
You’ve been acting strange lately.
Now that I’ve met Phrao again, I’ll never let her go.
I like you, Kaphrao.
I like her too.
♫I still remember vividly that day when we first met♫
♫Those memories we had together never fade away from my heart♫
♫We might never say it out loud how we feel for each other♫
♫But deep down we both know how we feel♫
♫Those things in the past, I still can’t forget them♫
♫I want to know if you’re like that too–do you also feel the same?♫
♫I could never forget those eyes of yours♫
♫The warmth you used to give me, I still remember it vividly♫
♫No matter for how long, you’ll always remain in my heart♫
♫All those years I’ve been waiting, for us to finally be together again♫
[North Star Entertainment]
[Flaming Chains of Love]